A Guide to the Secretary of Administration, Records, 1998-2001
Library of Virginia
- Y2K Project Office Files (Century Date Change Initiative Project Office) 1996-1999
  - Office Files 1996-1999
    - Correspondence, 1996 to 1997 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, January to August 1998 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, September 1998 to December 1999 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Memorandums, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Memorandums, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Records (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - CDCI Task Force Records 1998
    - Minutes of 3 March 1998 Meeting (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Minutes of 2 June 1998 Meeting (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Agenda of 7 July 1998 Meeting (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - CDCI Steering Committee Records 1998-1999
    - Steering Committee Agenda - 9 July 1998 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Steering Committee Agenda - 5 November 1998 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Steering Committee Agenda - 19 November 1998 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Steering Committee Agenda - 17 December 1998 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Steering Committee Agenda - 18 February 1999 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Steering Committee Agenda - 17 March 1999 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Steering Committee Agenda - 15 April 1999 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Steering Committee Agenda - 20 May 1999 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Steering Committee Agenda - 17 June 1999 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Steering Committee Agenda - 22 July 1999 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Steering Committee Agenda - 19 August 1999 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Steering Committee Agenda - 9 September 1999 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Steering Committee Agenda - 7 October 1999 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Steering Committee Agenda - 4 November 1999 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Administration Secretariat Year 2000 Task Force 1998
    - Agenda and Notes of 9 April 1998 Meeting (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Agenda and Notes of 14 May 1998 Meeting (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Agenda and Notes of 11 June 1998 Meeting (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Agenda and Notes of 9 July 1998 Meeting (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Reports 1998-1999
    - CDCI Project Office - Quarterly Report, January - March 1999 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - CDCI Project Office - Quarterly Report, April - June 1999 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - CDCI Project Office - Quarterly Report, July - September 1999 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - CDCI Project Office - Quarterly Report, 1 October 1999 - 1 January 2000 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - High Risk Agencies and Institutions, March and April 1998 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Year 2000 Progress Reports - Secretary of Administration, May 1998 to October 1999 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Year 2000 Readiness Disclosure Statement - Charitable Gaming Commission (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Year 2000 Readiness Review Reports - Commission on Local Government (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Year 2000 Readiness Review Reports - Commonwealth Competition Council (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Year 2000 Readiness Review Reports - Compensation Board (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Year 2000 Readiness Review Reports - Council on Human Rights (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Year 2000 Readiness Review Reports - Department of Employee Relations Counselors (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Year 2000 Readiness Review Reports - Department of General Services (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Year 2000 Readiness Review Reports - Department of Personnel and Training (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Year 2000 Readiness Review Reports - Department for Rights of Virginians with Disabilities (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Year 2000 Readiness Review Reports - Department of Veterans' Affairs (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Year 2000 Readiness Review Reports - State Board of Elections (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Plans 1999
    - Issue Summary of the Secretarial Contingency Planning Work Sessions, 8 November 1999 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Y2K Emergency Response and Recovery Plan, 3 December 1999 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Council on Information Management 1996-1998
    - Meeting Records, 6 February 1998 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Meeting Records, 3 April 1998 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Virginia Information Providers Network Authority (VIPNET), 1998 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Network Virginia, 1996-1997 (Governor George Allen's Administration) (Box 14, Folder 51)
- Special Projects File - Census Project 2000
  - Records, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Special Projects Files - Military Voting Project 2001
  - Records, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Intellectual Property Reports 1995-2001
  - 1995-1997 (Governor George Allen's Administration) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - 2001 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Assessment of State and Federal Mandates on Local Government
  - 1998 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 1999 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - February - July 2000 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - August - September 2000 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - October - December 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - January - April 2001 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - May - November 2001 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Federal Legislative Reports, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Real Property Files - Main Street Station 1995-2000
  - Correspondence and Memorandums, 1995 (Governor George Allen Administration) (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Main Street Station Feasibility Study, March 1995 (Allen Administration) (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Memorandums and Clippings, 1998-2000 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - City of Richmond - Proposal to the Honorable James S. Gilmore, III and the Virginia General Assembly to Acquire the Main Street Station, 24 November 1999 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - E-COM, Plan and Project Design for the Removal and Disposal of Asbestos Containing Materials and Lead-Based Paint at the Main Street Station Head House, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Executive Mansion Renovation 1998-2001
  - Studies
    - Long Range Improvement Planning Study for the Executive Mansion, ca. 1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Electronic Mail 1998-2000
    - 1999 June 26 - 2000 December 7 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - 1999 June 25 - 1998 August 12 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Organizations
    - Capitol Square Preservation Council (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Foundation for the Preservation of Virginia's Executive Mansion, Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Foundation for the Preservation of Virginia's Executive Mansion, Invoices (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Garden Club of Virginia (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Project Records
    - Appraisement of Personal Property Belonging to Commonwealth of Virginia, Executive Mansion, 1998 April 6 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Architectural-Engineering Services Proposals - Hanbury Evans Newill Vlattas and Company, 1998 May 26 and Interview Notes (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Construction Management Proposals - Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Construction Management Proposals - Daniel and Company, Inc., 1998 April 30 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, Agenda and Reports, Renovations to the Executive Mansion, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - FOIA Request, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Governor's Temporary Housing (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous/Unidentified (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Presentations and Project Updates, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Punch Lists, Move Schedules, etc., 1999-2001 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Storage, Personal Belongins, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Articles
    - 1998-1999 (part one) (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - 1998-1999 (part two) (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - 1981-1990 (articles on previous renovations) (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous 1998
    - Camp Pendleton Repairs, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Bob Vila 1998-1999
    - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Video of Bob Vila's Home Again, Renovation of the Executive Mansion, Show #1014 1999 December 6 (Box 17)
    - Video of Bob Vila's Home Again, Renovation of the Executive Mansion, Show #1015 1999 December 13 (Box 17)
    - Video of Bob Vila's Home Again, Renovation of the Executive Mansion, Show #1016 1999 December 20 (Box 17)
    - Video of Bob Vila's Home Again, Renovation of the Executive Mansion, Show #1017 1999 December 27 (Box 17)
    - Video of Bob Vila's Home Again, Renovation of the Executive Mansion, Show #1018 2000 January 3 (Box 17)
    - Video of Bob Vila's Home Again, Renovation of the Executive Mansion, Show #1019 2000 January 10 (Box 17)
    - Video of Bob Vila's Home Again, Renovation of the Executive Mansion, Show #1020 2000 January 17 (Box 17)
    - Video of Bob Vila's Home Again, Renovation of the Executive Mansion, Show #1021 2000 January 24 (Box 17)
    - Video of Bob Vila's Home Again, Renovation of the Executive Mansion, Show #1022 2000 January 31 (Box 17)
    - Video of Bob Vila's Home Again, Renovation of the Executive Mansion, Show #1023 2000 February 7 (Box 17)
    - Video of Bob Vila's Home Again, Renovation of the Executive Mansion, Show #1024 2000 February 14 (Box 17)
    - Video of Bob Vila's Home Again, Renovation of the Executive Mansion, Show #1025 2000 February 21 (Box 17)
    - Video of Bob Vila's Home Again, Renovation of the Executive Mansion, Show #1026 2000 February 28 (Box 17)
    - Video of Bob Vila's Home Again, Renovation of the Executive Mansion, Episdoes 1-4 (Box 17)
    - Video of Bob Vila's Home Again, Renovation of the Executive Mansion, Episodes 5-8 (Box 17)
    - Video of Bob Vila's Home Again, Renovation of the Executive Mansion, Episodes 9-12 (Box 17)
    - Video of Bob Vila's Home Again, Renovation of the Executive Mansion, Episode 13 (Box 17)
  - Oversize - Located in Map Case 24, Drawer 14
    - Site Improvements Information Handbook, Executive Mansion, 1999 June 14 (2 copies)
    - Project Schedule, Renovations to the Executive Mansion, by Daniel and Company, Construction Manager, 1998 June 29
    - Blue Prints for the Restoration of the Executive Mansion, 1998 October (RESTRICTED)